jackjones.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy policy - read about privacy policy for JACK & JONES

Please note that we will currently answer the phone in English, as we have very limited availability of Spanish language agents. Emails in Spanish will be replied to in Spanish.

We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you.

###### Collection of personal data

BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. Vijzelstraat 68-78 1017 HL Amsterdam, Holland collects and processes personal data in accordance with applicable data protection law.

At BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. we take privacy and security concerns seriously. At the same time, we would like to give you the best possible experience when visiting our websites. Therefore, we collect some information that we use when you are shopping on the BESTSELLER online shop. This could for example be information on which pages you go to and which features you click on.

You will be notified before any personal data about you is collected. The personal data we collect includes your name, phone number, e-mail address, private address, shopping information and your payment details.

BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. collects and processes personal data in accordance with applicable data protection law.

###### What does BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. use the data for?

BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. collects the personal data to be used for the BESTSELLER online shop, for executing orders, for signing you up for requested features etc. and to send marketing material and other information regarding our products and activities. Furthermore, your data can be used for fraud detection purposes. 

Your e-mail address is collected so that we can send you an order confirmation and inform you when your order has been shipped. Your name and phone number will be put on a label on the outside of the parcel with your order. This is done so that BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. or our external shipping providers can contact you if there are any questions or problems during the shipping process, or in order to inform you that your order has arrived. 

If you are a member of BESTSELLER’s customer club, BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. may pass on and receive customer and membership information and information on purchased goods to and from BESTSELLER A/S in Denmark with the purpose of improving the shopping experience for BESTSELLER’s customers and to improve and target the marketing we send to you.

BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. will process your personal data for marketing purposes subject to applicable laws, including legislation on obtaining consent for electronic marketing.

###### Cookies

BESTSELLER* uses cookies to give you the best possible experience when you visit our website. A cookie is a small text file which is attached to your computer's hard disk, smartphone or other IT equipment. It enables your computer/IP address to be recognised and information to be collected regarding the pages and functions you visit.

The first time you visit our website, you will see a banner at the top with the statement that we use cookies. If you do not want us to use cookies at all, you must deactivate cookies in your browser. However, you should be aware that in this case there may be services and functions which you cannot use as they require cookies to remember the choices you are making. You can follow the link below if you would like instructions on how to delete cookies from your browser.

BESTSELLER uses cookies to give you a better user experience on our website, to remember the choices you are making when you use our website, for example choice of country, and for ongoing improvement of the content and functions you experience on our website. We also use cookies to target our marketing so that it matches your requirements, and to generate statistics regarding the use of our website.

Some cookies are kept until you close down your browser, while others are kept for longer.

BESTSELLER makes use of third-party cookies. A third-party cookie is a cookie which is installed by someone other than BESTSELLER, such as other websites which provide content for our website, suppliers of some of our functions on the website or analysis programmes. Below you can see a list of the third-party cookies we use. 

Google Analytics, Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA  
Demandware Inc., 5 Wall St., Burlington, MA 01803, USA  
AddThis, 1595 Spring Hill Rd, Suite 300, Vienna, VA 22182

BESTSELLER will occasionally show content from YouTube. YouTube may therefore place cookies, including third-party cookies, over which BESTSELLER has no influence. BESTSELLER has no knowledge of the identity or purpose of such cookies. If you want to know more about which cookies are used by YouTube, you can see their cookie policy [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/cookies/). 

If you use a link from BESTSELLER's websites to a third-party's website, you should be aware that new cookies may be used over which BESTSELLER has no influence. In this case you should investigate the website's cookie policy yourself. 

Links to remove cookies via browser settings: 

*: BESTSELLER comprises BESTSELLER A/S, VILA A/S and BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V.

###### Security

BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. has implemented a number of security measures to ensure that our internal procedures comply with the security standards required in accordance with applicable data protection law. BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. always strives to protect your personal data in the best possible way.

###### Your rights

You are entitled to access data about you which is processed by BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V., however, subject to certain statutory exemptions. You are also entitled to object to the collection and further processing of your personal data. In addition, you are always entitled to have potentially incorrect personal data corrected.

###### Change of information or deregistration, etc.

If you want us to update, change or delete personal data which we have registered about you or if you do not want to receive additional messages from us or if you have questions regarding the above guidelines, please contact us at [customerservice@bestseller.com](mailto:customerservice@bestseller.com)

###### Transfer to third parties

Your personal data may be transferred to BESTSELLER's warehouses in Germany and Denmark for packing and sending your items as well as to BESTSELLER A/S in Denmark for marketing and customer services such as handling returns or complaints. Furthermore, your personal data will be transferred to our external business partners that we use in order to process and ship your order. 

We would like to point out that legislation and regulations relating to the safeguarding, processing and transmission of personal data may be different in other countries from the related provisions in the Netherlands. By providing your personal data, you agree to your data being transmitted abroad in accordance with this provision.

###### Deletion

BESTSELLER HANDELS B.V. will process and store your personal data for as long as it is necessary and permitted under applicable data protection law.

###### Disputes

Dutch legislation regulates any circumstances or any disputes, which may occur in connection with usage of the website.

Back to top
